{
    "subject": "resource/Broadminded_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/studio",
    "object": "resource/First_National",
    "human_readable": "The film Broadminded was produced by First National.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9034422039985657,
            "question": "Which film was produced by First National?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883137702941895,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Broadminded and First National?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8700997233390808,
            "question": "Who produced the film Broadminded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677978515625,
            "question": "Name a film produced by First National."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8627015352249146,
            "question": "What is the relationship between First National and the film Broadminded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7043654322624207,
            "question": "Was Broadminded a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6013138294219971,
            "question": "How influential was First National in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5286162495613098,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any other films produced by First National?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4678795039653778,
            "question": "What does the production company name, First National, suggest about their approach to filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4432520866394043,
            "question": "What is the name of the production company behind Broadminded?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Broadminded was produced by First National.",
            "html": "dbpedia_232_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the production company name, First National, suggest about their approach to filmmaking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_232_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any other films produced by First National?",
            "html": "dbpedia_232_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How influential was First National in the film industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_232_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_232_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states \"Original Film Title: BROADMINDED.  English Title: BROADMINDED.  Film Director: MERVYN LEROY.  Year: 1931.\". It also states \"Production Company: First National\" .  This strongly supports the triple that The film Broadminded was produced by First National. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that the film \"Broadminded\" (also known as \"BROAD MINDED\") was indeed produced by First National, with various details such as director Mervyn LeRoy, star Joe E. Brown, and release year 1931."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the film \"Broadminded\" was produced by First National, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}